♪The stars remember♪
♪Die Sterne erinnern sich♪
♪The promise we made to each other♪
♪Das Versprechen, das wir uns gegenseitig gegeben haben♪
♪Every breeze carries your touch♪
♪Jede Brise trägt deine Berührung♪
♪Kissing the warmth of my hand♪
♪Küsse die Wärme meiner Hand♪
♪So no matter how far it may be, don't hesitate♪
♪ Also, egal wie weit es ist, zögere nicht ♪
♪Love will guide us through♪
♪Die Liebe wird uns durchbringen♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪Wenn der Sternenpfad zum Ende des Lichtjahres führt♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪Hätte ich dich etwas früher kennengelernt?♪
♪Like night embracing the fireworks" glow♪
♪Wie die Nacht, die das Feuerwerk umarmt♪
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪Du und ich sollten Händchen halten♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪Wenn der Sternenpfad zum Ende des Lichtjahres führt♪
♪Would destiny have brought us together?♪
♪Hätte uns das Schicksal zusammengeführt?♪
♪Turning thorns into silver threads on a crown♪
♪Dornen in Silberfäden für eine Krone verwandeln♪
♪I'll weave them for you, forever around♪
♪Ich werde sie für dich weben, für immer um dich herum♪
=Long Planned Love=
=Lang geplante Liebe=
=Episode 15=
=Folge 15=
Bed rest for pregnancy?
Bettruhe während der Schwangerschaft?
Because I'm just two months pregnant.
Weil ich erst im zweiten Monat schwanger bin.
The baby is unstable.
Das Baby ist instabil.
I crashed into Jian Cheng's car,
Ich bin in Jian Chengs Auto gekracht,
so I may have a miscarriage.
also kann es sein, dass ich eine Fehlgeburt habe.
Jian Cheng hit you first, right?
Jian Cheng hat Sie zuerst geschlagen, richtig?
If it hadn't been Jian Cheng,
Wenn es nicht Jian Cheng gewesen wäre,
I wouldn't be here now.
Ich wäre jetzt nicht hier.
I'm sorry.
Es tut mir Leid.
The person you called is busy making money.
Die Person, die Sie angerufen haben, ist damit beschäftigt, Geld zu verdienen.
Please send a transfer if it's urgent.
Bitte überweisen Sie in dringenden Fällen.
Jian Cheng.
Jian Cheng.
That was so cruel of you.
Das war so grausam von dir.
You can't have kids yourself,
Du kannst selbst keine Kinder haben,
so you went after Yufeng's child.
also hast du es auf Yufengs Kind abgesehen.
Yufeng is right not to choose you.
Yufeng hat Recht, Sie nicht zu wählen.
Cao Ying, what are you saying?
Cao Ying, was sagst du?
You'd better hope Jiang Yawei's baby is fine.
Sie sollten besser hoffen, dass es Jiang Yaweis Baby gut geht.
- What? - Or I won't let this slide.
- Was? - Oder ich lasse das nicht durchgehen.
You've hurt my grandson.
Sie haben meinem Enkel wehgetan.
An innocent life.
Ein unschuldiges Leben.
Even Zhou Tingyan can't shield you this time.
Nicht einmal Zhou Tingyan kann Sie dieses Mal beschützen.
No, Cao Ying, you...
Nein, Cao Ying, du ...
(Wow, throwing insults and running off.)
(Wow, Beleidigungen um sich werfen und wegrennen.)
(How shameless can they be?)
(Wie schamlos können sie sein?)
(Wait a sec.)
(Warte eine Sekunde.)
No way, I can't go.
Auf keinen Fall, ich kann nicht gehen.
Or I'll end up fighting with Cao Ying.
Oder ich werde am Ende mit Cao Ying kämpfen.
If I get hurt, Zhou Tingyan will be upset.
Wenn ich verletzt werde, wird Zhou Tingyan verärgert sein.
Hey.
Hey.
Honey.
Honig.
Someone's picking on me.
Jemand hat es auf mir abgesehen.
It's fine, I'll stand up for you.
Es ist in Ordnung, ich werde für Sie eintreten.
Mm.
Mm.
Set up a family group chat.
Richten Sie einen Familiengruppenchat ein.
(Zhou Lu) Invite all the Zhou family members
(Zhou Lu) Lade alle Mitglieder der Familie Zhou ein
to the group chat.
zum Gruppenchat.
(Zhou Tingyan) Got it, on it now.
(Zhou Tingyan) Verstanden, jetzt dran.
The audience is all here.
Das Publikum ist vollständig hier.
(Zhou Tingyan) This is the security footage.
(Zhou Tingyan) Dies ist das Überwachungsvideo.
Post it in the group.
Poste es in der Gruppe.
No need to hold back.
Kein Grund, sich zurückzuhalten.
Say whatever you want.
Sagen Sie, was Sie wollen.
I've got your back.
Ich stehe hinter dir.
Impressive.
Beeindruckend.
Baichuan, you need to step in and stop this.
Baichuan, Sie müssen eingreifen und das stoppen.
A child unraised is the parent's fault.
Ein nicht erzogenes Kind ist die Schuld der Eltern.
(Zhou Family) A wife's failing is the husband's fault.
(Familie Zhou) Das Versagen einer Ehefrau ist die Schuld des Ehemannes.
This is on me. I'm sorry.
Das geht auf meine Kappe. Es tut mir leid.
I'll come by to apologize in person.
Ich werde vorbeikommen, um mich persönlich zu entschuldigen.
Your mom would never admit she's wrong.
Deine Mutter würde niemals zugeben, dass sie Unrecht hat.
Just apologize on your mom's behalf.
Entschuldige dich einfach im Namen deiner Mutter.
And send Jian Cheng a few red packets.
Und schicken Sie Jian Cheng ein paar rote Päckchen.
You and your wife owe an apology too.
Auch Sie und Ihre Frau schulden uns eine Entschuldigung.
Dad, if we apologize, we'll lose dignity.
Papa, wenn wir uns entschuldigen, verlieren wir unsere Würde.
I've posted an apology in the group.
Ich habe in der Gruppe eine Entschuldigung gepostet.
Not apologizing is a slap in my face.
Sich nicht zu entschuldigen ist ein Schlag ins Gesicht für mich.
Uncle Zhou crossed the line.
Onkel Zhou hat die Grenze überschritten.
You've always treated him well.
Sie haben ihn immer gut behandelt.
Yet he dragged you into the mess.
Und doch hat er Sie in das Chaos hineingezogen.
What a fool.
Was für ein Idiot.
Only if I step in will this mess end.
Nur wenn ich eingreife, wird dieses Chaos ein Ende haben.
Uncle Zhou is doing this to save my face.
Onkel Zhou tut das, um mein Gesicht zu wahren.
He's giving you an exit.
Er gibt Ihnen einen Ausgang.
Nice.
Hübsch.
(Zhou Family)
(Familie Zhou)
(Tingyan is actually defending Jian Cheng.)
(Tingyan verteidigt tatsächlich Jian Cheng.)
You're such bad luck.
Du hast so ein Pech.
Ever since you married in,
Seit Sie geheiratet haben,
we haven't had a single good day.
wir hatten keinen einzigen guten Tag.
Yufeng's job was taken
Yufengs Job wurde übernommen
by Zhou Lu because of you.
von Zhou Lu wegen dir.
You made me look bad in front of those wealthy madams.
Sie haben dafür gesorgt, dass ich vor diesen reichen Damen schlecht aussehe.
Even Yufeng's dad got embarrassed.
Sogar Yufengs Vater geriet in Verlegenheit.
You only bring trouble.
Du bringst nur Ärger.
You're a walking disaster.
Du bist eine wandelnde Katastrophe.
Mom.
Mama.
Yawei's still pregnant.
Yawei ist immer noch schwanger.
I didn't lie.
Ich habe nicht gelogen.
If it weren't for Jian Cheng, I wouldn't be like this.
Ohne Jian Cheng wäre ich nicht so.
You... just wait and see.
Sie... warten Sie einfach ab.
Mom, please step outside first.
Mama, geh bitte zuerst nach draußen.
Zhou Lu...
Zhou Lu...
Zhou Lu, what do you mean?
Zhou Lu, what do you mean?
You just do whatever Uncle Zhou says.
You just do whatever Uncle Zhou says.
Unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
Do we have that many people in our family?
Do we have that many people in our family?
What, they're popping out of coffins?
What, they're popping out of coffins?
Oh, there are plenty.
Oh, there are plenty.
Your mom's aunts, uncles, and your granduncle.
Your mom's aunts, uncles, and your granduncle.
The list keeps going.
The list keeps going.
Uncle Zhou is in the group.
Uncle Zhou is in the group.
Perfect chance to make some connections.
Perfect chance to make some connections.
I'm even thinking of bringing in
I'm even thinking of bringing in
the single nephew of my aunt's son-in-law.
the single nephew of my aunt's son-in-law.
Lots of single ladies in the group.
Lots of single ladies in the group.
We could just set them up.
We could just set them up.
If you can't handle it, leave the group.
If you can't handle it, leave the group.
But let me warn you.
But let me warn you.
Uncle Zhou actually tagged you all.
Uncle Zhou actually tagged you all.
Better apologize before you leave.
Better apologize before you leave.
Do like I did.
Do like I did.
Send a message.
Send a message.
Just a "sorry" will do.
Just a "sorry" will do.
No need to say more.
No need to say more.
I didn't say Jian Cheng was involved.
I didn't say Jian Cheng was involved.
It was your mom who misunderstood.
It was your mom who misunderstood.
Clearly, she wanted to target Jian Cheng.
Clearly, she wanted to target Jian Cheng.
And she even hit me.
And she even hit me.
Why should I apologize?
Why should I apologize?
My dad already apologized.
My dad already apologized.
Not apologizing is disrespecting him.
Not apologizing is disrespecting him.
You're saving face for my dad.
You're saving face for my dad.
I'm fed up with this.
I'm fed up with this.
Stop stirring up trouble.
Stop stirring up trouble.
I'll get you some med.
I'll get you some med.
(Zhou Family)
(Zhou Family)
On behalf of my mom, I apologize to you.
On behalf of my mom, I apologize to you.
- Sorry.
- Sorry.
(Zhou Family)
(Zhou Family)
That video really was shocking.
That video really was shocking.
Yufeng, lay off driving. You're risking others.
Yufeng, lay off driving. You're risking others.
Mrs. Zhou, how could you not let us know?
Mrs. Zhou, how could you not let us know?
Something this big happened.
Something this big happened.
(Best Wishes) I didn't even visit you.
(Best Wishes) I didn't even visit you.
That's really a shame.
That's really a shame.
I sent you a red envelope.
I sent you a red envelope.
Get something to recover.
Get something to recover.
(Honey) Keep this group.
(Honey) Keep this group.
(Zhou Tingyan) Add anyone
(Zhou Tingyan) Add anyone
(Best Wishes) bothers you in.
(Best Wishes) bothers you in.
Let them lose face.
Let them lose face.
(Zhou Tingyan) Generous, honey.
(Zhou Tingyan) Generous, honey.
This group will be my Judgment Court.
This group will be my Judgment Court.
I'll spend a little to keep it running well.
I'll spend a little to keep it running well.
(Generous, honey.)
(Generous, honey.)
You had Zhou Lu make the group to back her up?
You had Zhou Lu make the group to back her up?
That's right.
That's right.
It's fine if you want to help her out.
It's fine if you want to help her out.
Just make a group
Just make a group
and only invite people in Jiangyu.
and only invite people in Jiangyu.
Why drag in all those
Why drag in all those
messy connections?
messy connections?
You can't ignore our family's reputation
You can't ignore our family's reputation
just for something this minor.
just for something this minor.
That road only had her car at the time.
That road only had her car at the time.
You should be glad there were no other cars.
You should be glad there were no other cars.
If Yufeng had gone through with that move,
If Yufeng had gone through with that move,
what would the outcome've been?
what would the outcome've been?
Just picturing it in makes me...
Just picturing it in makes me...
She's endured so much.
She's endured so much.
So what if she lost her temper?
So what if she lost her temper?
But why make it a public spectacle?
But why make it a public spectacle?
Family troubles should stay within the family.
Family troubles should stay within the family.
Cao Ying cares most about dignity.
Cao Ying cares most about dignity.
I intend to strip her of that.
I intend to strip her of that.
She bullied Cheng before we married
She bullied Cheng before we married
and still dared to after our marriage.
and still dared to after our marriage.
I want everyone to know,
I want everyone to know,
Jian Cheng is not someone they can mess with.
Jian Cheng is not someone they can mess with.
Before they try to mess with her,
Before they try to mess with her,
they should ask me if I'll allow it.
they should ask me if I'll allow it.
Zhou Baichuan, you've never stood up for me.
Zhou Baichuan, Sie haben sich nie für mich eingesetzt.
The only time you showed guts
Das einzige Mal, dass du Mut gezeigt hast
is when you fought Dad over Guan Ling.
ist, als du mit Papa um Guan Ling gekämpft hast.
Why are you bringing her up?
Warum erwägst du sie?
What did she even do wrong?
Was hat sie überhaupt falsch gemacht?
I just can't stand her.
Ich kann sie einfach nicht ausstehen.
Why does she get everything
Warum bekommt sie alles
without lifting a finger?
ohne einen Finger zu rühren?
And now,
Und jetzt,
her son married the woman my son didn't want.
Ihr Sohn heiratete die Frau, die mein Sohn nicht wollte.
Finally, I feel vindicated.
Endlich fühle ich mich bestätigt.
Zhou Tingyan married Jian Cheng just to
Zhou Tingyan heiratete Jian Cheng, nur um
get back at Master Zhou for ruining his mother's life.
sich an Meister Zhou rächen, weil er das Leben seiner Mutter ruiniert hat.
Jian Cheng, that fool,
Jian Cheng, dieser Narr,
still thinks Zhou Tingyan loves her.
glaubt immer noch, dass Zhou Tingyan sie liebt.
She's nothing more than a pawn.
Sie ist nichts weiter als eine Schachfigur.
I'm just waiting to see her fall.
Ich warte nur darauf, sie fallen zu sehen.
(So,)
(Also,)
(Uncle Zhou married Jian Cheng just to spite Grandpa.)
(Onkel Zhou hat Jian Cheng nur geheiratet, um Opa zu ärgern.)
(Not out of affection.)
(Nicht aus Zuneigung.)
(It was all revenge.)
(Es war alles Rache.)
(Nephew) Want to know why he married you?
(Neffe) Möchten Sie wissen, warum er Sie geheiratet hat?
Tomorrow, 9 am.
Morgen, 9 Uhr.
Meet at the cafe at the end of East St.
Treffen Sie sich im Café am Ende der East St.
Cheng, Cheng.
Cheng, Cheng.
Tang.
Tang.
You really shouldn't go.
Du solltest wirklich nicht gehen.
Zhou Yufeng is salty
Zhou Yufeng ist salzig
about you calling him out in the group.
darüber, dass du ihn in der Gruppe herausgefordert hast.
He's holding a grudge.
Er hegt einen Groll.
Forget why Zhou Tingyan married you.
Vergiss, warum Zhou Tingyan dich geheiratet hat.
He's honestly been so good to you.
Er war wirklich so gut zu dir.
He's let you have your way.
Er hat Ihnen Ihren Willen gelassen.
Look, he even made a big scene today
Schauen Sie, er hat heute sogar eine große Szene gemacht
just to stand up for you.
nur um für dich einzustehen.
Right?
Rechts?
Pull yourself together.
Reiß dich zusammen.
Honestly, whatever the reason he married me,
Ehrlich gesagt, was auch immer der Grund war, warum er mich geheiratet hat,
I can live with it.
Ich kann damit leben.
So, are you still going or not?
Also, gehst du noch oder nicht?
Screenshot.
Screenshot.
(Honey)
(Honig)
(Nephew: Want to know why he married you?)
(Neffe: Willst du wissen, warum er dich geheiratet hat?)
(Meet me at the cafe at the end of East St.)
(Treffen wir uns im Café am Ende der East St.)
Meeting my ex-fiance alone is a big deal.
Meinen Ex-Verlobten alleine zu treffen, ist eine große Sache.
I should tell Zhou Tingyan first.
Ich sollte es zuerst Zhou Tingyan sagen.
Or he'll get mad once he finds out.
Oder er wird wütend, wenn er es herausfindet.
And he'll keep me up all night again.
Und er wird mich wieder die ganze Nacht wach halten.
Which means stress for nothing.
Das bedeutet Stress umsonst.
Tang.
Tang.
You said I've got Zhou Tingyan hooked.
Sie sagten, ich hätte Zhou Tingyan süchtig gemacht.
That's not true.
Das stimmt nicht.
Remember what I told you before?
Erinnern Sie sich, was ich Ihnen vorhin gesagt habe?
About that big client of Qianyi Group.
Über diesen großen Kunden der Qianyi Group.
Zhou Tingyan treats me really well now,
Zhou Tingyan behandelt mich jetzt wirklich gut,
but I still feel so much pressure.
aber ich fühle immer noch so viel Druck.
Cheng.
Cheng.
That Qianyi big client you mentioned
Der große Kunde Qianyi, den Sie erwähnt haben
sounds like someone I know.
klingt nach jemandem, den ich kenne.
Who?
WHO?
Kind of like one of Qin Zhuo's cousins.
So ähnlich wie einer von Qin Zhuos Cousins.
Her name's Qin Yingzhi.
Ihr Name ist Qin Yingzhi.
Wouldn't it be even riskier if it's her?
Wäre es nicht noch riskanter, wenn sie es wäre?
Stop overthinking.
Hören Sie auf, zu viel nachzudenken.
If it were Qin Yingzhi, that'd be fine.
Wenn es Qin Yingzhi wäre, wäre das in Ordnung.
To Zhou Tingyan, she's like Qin Zhuo.
Für Zhou Tingyan ist sie wie Qin Zhuo.
Just family, nothing more.
Nur Familie, mehr nicht.
But she made Zhou Lu suspicious.
Aber sie machte Zhou Lu misstrauisch.
This is exhausting.
Das ist anstrengend.
(Is Zhou Lu misleading Cheng?)
(Führt Zhou Lu Cheng in die Irre?)
(Why hasn't Zhou Tingyan replied yet?)
(Warum hat Zhou Tingyan noch nicht geantwortet?)
(He usually answers right away.)
(Normalerweise antwortet er sofort.)
Hey, Cheng.
Hey, Cheng.
I'm meeting Zhou Lu, see you.
Ich treffe mich mit Zhou Lu, wir sehen uns.
Jian Cheng.
Jian Cheng.
Yeah?
Ja?
There's something you should know.
Es gibt etwas, das Sie wissen sollten.
When my mom was in college, she went back to her high school
Als meine Mutter auf dem College war, ging sie zurück auf ihre High School
and met Zhou Baichuan.
und traf Zhou Baichuan.
He fell for her instantly.
Er verliebte sich sofort in sie.
My mom told him
Meine Mutter hat es ihm gesagt
she'd think about it.
sie würde darüber nachdenken.
But later, during a charity event,
Aber später, während einer Wohltätigkeitsveranstaltung,
she met Master Zhou.
Sie traf Meister Zhou.
After that, a lot happened.
Danach ist viel passiert.
My mother was forced to marry Master Zhou.
Meine Mutter wurde gezwungen , Meister Zhou zu heiraten.
Zhou Baichuan only found out at the wedding
Zhou Baichuan erfuhr es erst bei der Hochzeit
that the bride was my mother.
dass die Braut meine Mutter war.
They had a serious fallout.
Es kam zu schweren Auseinandersetzungen.
My mother lived in deep misery.
Meine Mutter lebte in tiefem Elend.
Master Zhou locked away all her youth and freedom.
Meister Zhou hat ihre ganze Jugend und Freiheit weggesperrt .
What Zhou Yufeng means is
Was Zhou Yufeng meint, ist
his father took the woman my father loved.
sein Vater nahm mir die Frau, die mein Vater liebte.
He thought I'd seek revenge
Er dachte, ich würde Rache nehmen
and take his wife.
und ihm seine Frau nehmen.
Zhou Tingyan.
Zhou Tingyan.
I know.
Ich weiß.
It's not revenge.
Es ist keine Rache.
(Zhou Tingyan,)
(Zhou Tingyan,)
(let's heal)
(Lass uns heilen)
(all our wounds.)
(alle unsere Wunden.)
Jian Cheng, that fool,
Jian Cheng, dieser Narr,
still thinks Zhou Tingyan loves her.
glaubt immer noch, dass Zhou Tingyan sie liebt.
She's nothing more than a pawn.
Sie ist nichts weiter als eine Schachfigur.
I'm just waiting to see her fall.
Ich warte nur darauf, sie fallen zu sehen.
What did that "one" you sent me mean?
Was bedeutete das „eins“, das Sie mir geschickt haben?
"One" means
„Eins“ bedeutet
you made me mad, so you lost a point.
du hast mich wütend gemacht, deshalb hast du einen Punkt verloren.
From now on, every time you annoy me,
Von nun an, jedes Mal, wenn du mich ärgerst,
you lose one point.
Sie verlieren einen Punkt.
When you've lost a full hundred,
Wenn du volle hundert verloren hast,
I'll no longer love you.
Ich werde dich nicht mehr lieben.
(After leaving me,)
(Nachdem er mich verlassen hat,)
(life hasn't been great for you either.)
(Das Leben war auch für Sie nicht so toll.)
I told her about Master Zhou forcing the marriage.
Ich erzählte ihr, dass Meister Zhou die Heirat erzwungen hatte.
(Jian Cheng) Enjoy your coffee.
(Jian Cheng) Genießen Sie Ihren Kaffee.
Don't play these tricks again.
Spielen Sie diese Tricks nicht noch einmal.
If you still call yourself a man,
Wenn du dich immer noch einen Mann nennst,
come to me directly.
komm direkt zu mir.
I'm Zhou Tingyan.
Ich bin Zhou Tingyan.
(With this child,)
(Mit diesem Kind)
(I can find my place in the Zhou Family.)
(Ich kann meinen Platz in der Familie Zhou finden.)
(I've worked so hard for this.)
(Ich habe so hart dafür gearbeitet.)
(Finally, I've reached this point.)
(Endlich bin ich an diesem Punkt angelangt.)
(Nothing can go wrong with this baby.)
(Mit diesem Baby kann nichts schiefgehen.)
Mom.
Mama.
Drink up.
Trink aus.
What is this?
Was ist das?
It's a secret formula for having a son.
Es ist eine Geheimformel, um einen Sohn zu bekommen.
It's very effective.
Es ist sehr effektiv.
Drink it while it's hot.
Trinken Sie es, solange es heiß ist.
It's half as effective when it cools.
Wenn es abkühlt, ist es nur halb so effektiv.
Mom, the doctor said,
Mama, sagte der Arzt,
those folk remedies are all scams.
Diese Volksheilmittel sind allesamt Schwindel.
Blindly taking medicine is harmful.
Die blinde Einnahme von Medikamenten ist schädlich.
Besides, I'm already hospitalized.
Außerdem bin ich bereits im Krankenhaus.
Let's listen to the doctor.
Hören wir auf den Arzt.
Just drink it.
Trink es einfach.
You're carrying my grandson.
Sie tragen meinen Enkel.
Would I hurt you?
Würde ich dir wehtun?
If it weren't for my grandson,
Wenn mein Enkel nicht wäre,
you think I'd be waiting on you?
denkst du, ich würde auf dich warten?
Drink.
Trinken.
Just drink when I tell you to.
Trinken Sie einfach, wenn ich es Ihnen sage.
That's more like it.
Das trifft es schon eher.
- Mom. - Yeah.
- Mama. - Ja.
Yawei.
Jahwe.
Why do you look so pale?
Warum siehst du so blass aus?
Mom, what's wrong with Yawei?
Mama, was ist mit Yawei los?
Morning sickness.
Morgenübelkeit.
All women go through it.
Alle Frauen machen das durch.
No need to make a fuss.
Kein Grund, Aufhebens zu machen.
(The next day)
(Am nächsten Tag)
Yawei.
Jahwe.
Mom said your morning sickness is bad.
Mama hat gesagt, deine Morgenübelkeit ist schlimm.
I've noticed you've lost lots of weight.
Mir ist aufgefallen, dass Sie viel Gewicht verloren haben.
My mom said,
Meine Mutter sagte:
she'll take care of your meals.
Sie kümmert sich um Ihre Mahlzeiten.
That way,
Auf diese Weise,
I can rest easy.
Ich kann beruhigt sein.
It's only been two months.
Es sind erst zwei Monate vergangen.
How bad can the sickness be?
Wie schlimm kann die Krankheit sein?
I ended up like this
Ich bin so geendet
because of your mom's secret recipe.
wegen des Geheimrezepts deiner Mutter.
Yufeng,
Yufeng,
can you tell your mom
kannst du es deiner Mutter sagen
to stop making me drink that stuff?
damit ich nicht mehr gezwungen werde, das Zeug zu trinken?
Every time I drink it, I throw up.
Jedes Mal, wenn ich es trinke, muss ich mich übergeben.
And my stomach hurts.
Und mein Magen tut weh.
If this goes on,
Wenn das so weitergeht,
I'm afraid I might really…
Ich habe Angst, dass ich wirklich …
Yawei, just listen to her.
Yawei, hör ihr einfach zu.
She's doing it for the sake of our baby.
Sie tut es zum Wohle unseres Babys.
No matter how much she dislikes you,
Egal, wie sehr sie dich nicht mag,
she'd never do anything to harm the child.
Sie würde dem Kind niemals etwas antun.
Besides, this is a good chance
Außerdem ist dies eine gute Chance
to improve things between you.
um die Dinge zwischen euch zu verbessern.
You can't keep giving the cold shoulder.
Sie können nicht immer die kalte Schulter zeigen.
Come on, be good.
Komm schon, sei brav.
♪Late at night, I count the fleeting seconds♪
♪Spät in der Nacht zähle ich die flüchtigen Sekunden♪
♪Among the crowd, I search for your gaze♪
♪Inmitten der Menge suche ich nach deinem Blick♪
♪How deep is the secret in my heart?♪
♪Wie tief ist das Geheimnis in meinem Herzen?♪
♪Drawing closer under the label of friends♪
♪ Unter dem Label „Freunde“ näher zusammenrücken ♪
♪I'm afraid to disturb your peace♪
♪Ich habe Angst, deinen Frieden zu stören♪
♪So I protect, never daring to ask for more♪
♪Also beschütze ich dich und wage es nie, nach mehr zu fragen♪
♪My eyes follow with a devotion♪
♪Meine Augen folgen mit Hingabe♪
♪It's the only thing I take to heart♪
♪Das ist das Einzige, was ich mir zu Herzen nehme♪
♪The heart is as fragile as glass♪
♪Das Herz ist so zerbrechlich wie Glas♪
♪Longing always comes during the night♪
♪Die Sehnsucht kommt immer in der Nacht♪
♪Tears at the corner of my eyes, a trembling voice♪
♪Tränen in den Augenwinkeln, eine zitternde Stimme♪
♪You walk right into my dreams again♪
♪Du kommst wieder direkt in meine Träume♪
♪Your love is a rare luxury♪
♪Deine Liebe ist ein seltener Luxus♪
♪So hard for me to reach♪
♪So schwer für mich zu erreichen♪
♪All I can do is let it settle down♪
♪Ich kann es nur zur Ruhe kommen lassen♪
♪Back to zero♪
♪Zurück auf Null♪